

LISA ISELIN

UI / UX Designer Graphic Designer

lisaiselin.com

UI/UX designer, strategic thinker, and optimistic team player with an innate sense of empathy and 10 years of graphic design experience. A self-motivated human with contagiously positive energy, a never-ending eagerness to learn, and a passion for solving problems. Familiar with UI/UX design processes, visual design, HTML, and CSS. Enthusiastically dead-set on having fun and becoming part of a growing team achieving greatness.



Contact



linkedin.com/in/lisaiselin



lisaiselin.com/contact



Skills & Tools

{ Hard Skills }

UX/UI Design & Process-Oriented

303.725.4769

lisaiselin@gmail.com

- Visual & Graphic Design
- Research & User Testing
- **Competitor Analysis**
- User Flows & Info. Architecture
- Prototypes & High Fidelity Mockups
- Wireframes
- Functional Pixel-Perfect Designs
- Problem Solving
- **Brand Identity & Development**
- Photo & Creative Art Direction
- Interactive Responsive Design

{ Soft Skills }

- Collaborative & Team-Oriented
- **Enthusiastically Self-Motivated**
- Integrity
- Innately Empathetic
- **Analytical Mindset**
- Eager to Learn
- Time & Project Management
- Adaptable
- **Process-Oriented**

{ **Tools** }

- Adobe XD
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- InVision
- GitHub
- Atom
- HTML5
- CSS3

Education

CareerFoundry

UI Design Immersion Certificate Frontend Dev Specialization Certificate

University of Minnesota

Bachelor of Science: Graphic Design **Emphasis:** Advertising



Hobbies











 $\supset \{Run\}$





Experience

Consulting & Freelance Design | 2005—Present { Iselin Design }

• UI/UX, visual design, and/or branding for a wide range of businesses and groups including, optimal performance consulting, chiropractic, physical therapy, construction, non-profit, startup, manufacturing, and lab equipment supplier for higher education markets

UI Designer Certification | August 2020—July 2021 { CareerFoundry }

- Developed and refined UX/UI skills, tools, and processes, gaining a better understanding of user needs and wants, resulting in a more intuitive, data-driven product
- Honed skillset designing products including human-centric ideas, research, identification of user problems, user flows, low to high fidelity wireframes, user testing, visual design, & prototypes
- Created interactive, responsive interfaces resulting in pleasant and seamless experiences focused on human-centric problem solving

Graphic Designer | 2017–2020

{ Globus }

- Sole redesign of B2B email campaigns resulting in increasing open rates by 100% and click-through rates 200% within 3 weeks of launch
- Upheld creative and brand standards on all collateral for 4 different Globus sub-brands targeting both direct and B2B customers
- Collaborated cross-functionally, and with B2B partners resulting in a cohesive clean product reflective of department and business goals

Production Manager | 2016–2017

{ Dish Network }

- Developed and managed Production Team designers
- Upheld corporate brand standards, maintaining quality assurance of all **Production Team projects**

Sr. Graphic Designer & Art Director | 2005–2016 { Sports Authority }

- Led and directed Creative Team members through entire creative process, concept, design, development, and execution of projects, brand and quarterly campaigns, and photoshoots resulting in a streamlined, cohesive message that inspired and resonated with customers
- · Art directed all facets of lifestyle and product photoshoots from concept and shoot plan development to on-set creative direction of photography and crew, producing final imagery aligned with brand messaging, invoking relatable and memorable impressions with consumers
- Collaborated and communicated cross-functionally, completing creatively aligned projects and deliverables in a quick and efficient time frame